<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Much Greener on Solidforest</title><link>https://solidforest.xyz/en/category/much-greener/</link><description>Recent content in Much Greener on Solidforest</description><generator>Solidforest -- solidforest.xyz</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 17:46:51 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://solidforest.xyz/en/category/much-greener/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Welcome Kodama</title><link>https://solidforest.xyz/en/welcome-kodama/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 17:46:51 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://solidforest.xyz/en/welcome-kodama/</guid><description>Kodama, you already know, that&amp;rsquo;s an iconic character from a Japanese legend. Although described as a small figure and dim in appearance, but his role is very big and noble. Protecting trees, protecting forests which also means protecting the world, I am serieous. It turns out that Japan is not only famous for its sushi, yes 😄 but also mythology that has local wisdom and good attitude for the environment.</description></item><item><title>Perfect Combo: Green Energy, Green Technology and Green Business</title><link>https://solidforest.xyz/en/green-energy-technology-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://solidforest.xyz/en/green-energy-technology-business/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="funding-support-for-building-green-energy">Funding Support for Building Green Energy&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;span class="dropcap text-primary bg-primary-soft">S&lt;/span>IFT is dedicated to advancing the sustainability and value of energy. Since 1999, Sustainable Energy Fund has worked tirelessly to build a sustainable energy future. Our mission is to promote, research and invest in clean and renewable energy technologies, energy conservation, energy efficiency and sustainable energy enterprises that provide opportunities and benefits. About us: SIFT is dedicated to advancing the sustainability and value of energy. Since 1999, Sustainable Energy Fund has worked tirelessly to build a sustainable energy future.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Affordable and Much Greener Furniture</title><link>https://solidforest.xyz/en/furniture-of-future/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://solidforest.xyz/en/furniture-of-future/</guid><description>We believe that wood is the best form of material for building furniture and we aim to help you make this furniture sustainably. We want to build sustainable and beautiful furniture. We believe in the value of wood, in the power of wood and in the beauty of wood. We are a small family-owned business. We want to build sustainable and beautiful furniture. We want to help you build sustainable and beautiful furniture.</description></item><item><title>The Sustainable Farm Project</title><link>https://solidforest.xyz/en/sustainable-food/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://solidforest.xyz/en/sustainable-food/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;span class="dropcap text-primary bg-primary-soft">T&lt;/span>here was a common misconception that farming methods have changed much since we first started using them. The truth is, just because there are more types of crops on the market doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean they have not changed in some form or another over time!&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>